

VIRENDRA KUMARYADAV

- Mumbai, India 401209
- 8149535304
- softech.vire@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Dedicated QA Automation bringing 4.3 years of experience and diligence to handle needs of large and complex products. Solid history in both manual and automated testing. Seek to apply expertise to growth-oriented, dynamic position.

Having aggressive to learn the new tools and technology which are more entertaining to our mind.

SKILLS

- Manual Testing
- · Scenarios and writing Cases
- · Automated Testing Frameworks
- · Test Plans and Test Methodologies
- Defect Tracking and Reporting
- · Continuous-Integration Testing
- · Teamwork and Positive Attitude
- · Web and Mobile Application QA

- · Scrum Methodology
- Software Development Tools: JIRA, Confluence
- Programming Languages: Java, HTMl Some knowledge of JS.
- Tools: Selenium, Cypress, MYSQl, Postman, Eclipes, Inteli-j, VS code, android Studio, Appium.
- Remote Tools: Git,GitHub, AzureDevops, GitLabs
- · Knowledge of Mobile Testing
- Having good Knowledge SQl and API testing by Postman tools
- Fremworks: POM, TestNG, BDD-Cucumber, API-Automation.

EXPERIENCE

QA AUTOMATION ENGINEER, 01/2022 – Current

Data Technology and Processing Corporation (INN-FLOW), Gurugram, Haryana, India

- Produced test scripts for new automated software testing rounds.
- Wrote and updated manual test cases for team use, maintaining optimal organization for maximum productivity and merge them and go for automation testscript.
- We also fellow agile so that we go on that process and fellow every steps like meetings, documentation
 and whatever prerequisite we have to prepare.
- I have witting end to end testcases and verify data as per task whatever i have provided.
- Created and optimized automated testing tools for repetitive tasks for regression.
- also prepare smoke testcases to automation.

QA ENGINEER, 08/2019 - 12/2021

SM Web Solutions Pvt. Ltd, New Delhi, India

- Collaborated with quality team members and leaders to monitor conformance to quality standards.
- Drafted process to standardized the writing of testscripts and techniques.
- · Supported QA Automation team in implementing corrective actions to increase quality.
- Having good collaborations to our manual team member.

PROJECTS

Discription

Konga is Nigeria's number one online shopping destination where you can shop the widest selection of electronics, fashion, home appliances, kid's items and more in Nigeria and have them shipped directly to your home or office at your convenience! We offer free nationwide delivery, free returns.

Rout4me(Locality) (10/2020 to 05/2021)

Discription

Route4me is an online Web service organisation that tells you the most efficient route to complete all your errands, just put in the addresses, and let it work its magic. Route4me optimizes your route when traveling to multiple destinations, allowing you to enter up to 200 addresses per route. Route4me claims that routes are usually shorter after being optimized. You can map the fastest or shortest path with Route4Me. The app could be particularly helpful for small business owners who regularly make multiple deliveries in a single trip. You could eyeball the map to pick the best route

Info crm (Back End Application) (06/2021 to 12/2021)

Discription

info crm is a back end application of organization, we have to here chake GUI as well as backend data and also chake API testing of the application .Its all about application making for manage the organization details.

Inn-flow.com (Hotel Management) (08/2019 to 10/2020)

Descriptions

It's a US based Hotel management product-based application, inside we maintain Sales and Procurements and We also maintain the Labour Data and all things related and also maintaining accounts.

EDUCATION AND TRAIING

Subharti University, Meerut, UP, 12/2022 **Master of Computer Application**

Thakur College of Science and commerce, Kandivali (west), Mumbai, 05/2016

Bachelor of Science: Science

Lokmanya Junior College, Vijay Nagar, Nallasopar, Mumbai., 05/2016 12th: Science

SMPDI College, Manikpur, UP, 05/2014

10th: Science

LANGUAGES

English:

Hindi:

Intermediate

Intermediate

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth

: 15-04-1998

Father's Name

: Mr.Kripashankar Yadav

Marital Status

: Unmerried

Gender

: Male